FRAN GARCIA / Drupal web developer

https://www.fjgarlin.com

I am an experienced Drupal web developer, specialised in long term maintenance of Drupal projects. I am really enthusiastic about what I do and enjoy solving problems, debugging and fixing code. I also enjoy helping and mentoring other people.

EXPERIENCE

Drupal Association (2021-current) - Remote Consultant Developer:

Drupal 6 to 9, Laravel...

Amazee Labs (2017-current) - Remote

Drupal Web Developer & Team Lead for the Global Maintenance Team: Maintenance & Support - Drupal 6 to 9, React, Gatsby, GraphQL...

IE Design Consultancy (2012-2017) - Birmingham, UK

Drupal Web Developer & Team Leader & Technical Manager: Drupal 6 to 8, Bootstrap, SASS...

Drupal certification

Friend MTS (2011-2012) - Birmingham, UK Web Developer: *Zend Framework, Smarty...*

Alia Multimedia (2010-2011) - Granada, Spain

Junior Web Developer: PHP, Smarty...

Escuela Arte Granada (2007-2010) - Granada, Spain

IT Teacher (Junior college level): Programming, Databases, Networking...

EDUCATION

Computer Science BSc (2003-2006) - University of Granada *First Class Honours*

Teaching certificate (2007) - University of Granada

LANGUAGES

English and Spanish (native)